[
    {
        "questionNo": "Q1.",
        "question": "Identify the qualitative adjective in the sentence: 'The old man sat on a creaky rocking chair.'",
        "options": [
            "Old",
            "Man",
            "Sat",
            "Creaky"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q2.",
        "question": "Which of the following is a quantitative adjective?",
        "options": [
            "Delightful",
            "Numerous",
            "Brilliant",
            "Eager"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q3.",
        "question": "'Several' is an adjective of a number.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q4.",
        "question": "'Gorgeous' is a quantitative adjective.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q5.",
        "question": "The ________ flowers in the garden were blooming beautifully.",
        "options": [
            "Colourful",
            "Decaying",
            "Withering",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q6.",
        "question": "There were ________ people at the concert last night.",
        "options": [
            "Countless",
            "Distant",
            "Green",
            "Silent"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q7.",
        "question": "Identify the demonstrative adjective in the sentence: 'Those books on the shelf belong to my sister.'",
        "options": [
            "Books",
            "Shelf",
            "Belong",
            "Those"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q8.",
        "question": "Which of the following is an interrogative adjective?",
        "options": [
            "Whose",
            "Beautiful",
            "Many",
            "How"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q9.",
        "question": "Identify the possessive adjective in the sentence: 'My friend's new car is very efficient.'",
        "options": [
            "New",
            "Car",
            "Efficient",
            "My"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q10.",
        "question": "'That' can be used as a demonstrative adjective.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q11.",
        "question": "'What kind' is an interrogative adjective.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q12.",
        "question": "Identify the qualitative adjective in the sentence: 'The delicious cake was baked to perfection.'",
        "options": [
            "The",
            "Cake",
            "Was",
            "Delicious"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q13.",
        "question": "Which of the following is a quantitative adjective?",
        "options": [
            "Bright",
            "Ample",
            "Intelligent",
            "Excited"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q14.",
        "question": "'Their' is a possessive adjective.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q15.",
        "question": "Identify the adjective of number in the sentence: 'The first three winners of the competition were awarded prizes.'",
        "options": [
            "The",
            "Three",
            "Winners",
            "Competition"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q16.",
        "question": "‘This’ is an _______ adjective.",
        "options": [
            "Possessive",
            "Demonstrative",
            "Qualitative",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q17.",
        "question": "‘Third’ is an ordinal adjective.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q18.",
        "question": "Identify the qualitative adjective in the sentence: 'The adventurous hiker explored the rugged terrain.'",
        "options": [
            "Explored",
            "Adventurous",
            "Rugged",
            "Both b and c"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q19.",
        "question": "‘Those’ and ‘Their’ are demonstrative adjectives.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q20.",
        "question": "‘Abundant’ is a _________ adjective.",
        "options": [
            "Qualitative",
            "Demonstrative",
            "Quantitative",
            "Possessive"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    }
]
